# JOSEF SIGNO







## PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

A self-starter and a quick learner. Versatile skill set with experience in customer service, fast-food, retail and written and oral communication. Over 4 years in Programming Experience. Recognized for quick learning, problem solving and initiative taking skills.

# **EDUCATION**

School of Engineering Technology Centennial College Scarborough, ON, Canada 2020-Present

Bachelor of Technology McMaster University Hamilton, ON, Canada 2015-2019

#### **GENERAL SKILLS**

- Flexible Time Management
- Problem Solving
- Teamwork
- Oral and Written Communication
- Attention to Detail
- Organizational Skills

## **COMPUTER SKILLS**

- Microsoft Excel
- C# Programming
- HTML Web Design
- JavaScript
- SCADA
- GIMP
- Blender

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### CAST MEMBER

Cineplex Entertainment | Ajax, Ontario, Canada | 2021-Present

- Operated the concession stand and took transactions from customers
- Prepared and served various foodstuffs to customers
- Helped prepare orders for delivery services like UberEats and Skip-The-Dishes
- Assisted guests with purchasing tickets, seating and any other issues they had
- Cleaned all work areas during closing hours while following sanitation routines

### FOOD COURT ASSOCIATE

Costco Wholesale | Oshawa, Ontario, Canada | 2019-2020

- Prepared and served various foods to members
- Helped cook pizzas in preparation for busy hours
- Restocked supplies in accordance to established routines, rotates food stocks, checks expiration dates
- Cleaned all work areas following sanitation routines
- Removal of trash, garbage, cardboard, milk and bread crates

## KITCHEN TEAM MEMBER

Jollibee Canada | Mississauga, Ontario, Canada | 2018-2019

- Knowledgeable of all menu products to quickly serve all customers
- Helped prepare orders for dine-in or to-go
- Prepared and handled foodstuffs using safe food handling procedures
- Operated the cash register, greeting customers and allowing them to feel welcome in the restaurant
- Routinely cleaned and sanitized dishware, flatware, trays, cups, glasses and cooking utensils

## PARK TEAM LEADER

Canada's Wonderland | Vaughan, Ontario, Canada | 2016-2018

- Provided prompt, courteous service by greeting and assisting guests
- Ensured the cleanliness of the designated park areas at all times
- Operated rides in the park in a safe and professional manner
- Loaded guests onto the rides and ensured they remained safe while the ride was in motion
- Ensured all team members followed proper operation proceedures and safetly protocols
- Created the rotational schedule for the team
- Lead a small group of 10-15 new members during the orientation program